Boss, what's wrong?
Yeah, tell us.
We'll help you figure something out.
Forget it.
Just leave.
Go.
I'm so angry my makeup is ruined.
Cangyue.
Get lost.
I won't.
You won't leave, right?
If you don't leave, I'll throw you off.
I won't leave even if you do.
You didn't...
Don't move. Go back.
I'm leaving.
I'm really leaving.
What are you doing?
Alright.
So annoying.
Just say what you want to say quickly.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry?
What? I have to get out just because you said so?
And I have to forgive you just because you said you're sorry?
I didn't know what was wrong with me.
I was a little out of control.
I apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
So are you free tonight?
This is the first person I killed with my own hands.
But my hands have long been stained with blood.
I have let down too many people in my life.
Your Majesty.
Do it.
But... but he made no grave mistake.
If he can knock over a candlestick today,
he'll dare to set Zhaoyang Hall on fire tomorrow.
If you can't bring yourself to do it,
I'll have to execute his entire family for you.
You have to choose one.
Your Majesty, I grew up with you
and have seen countless splendors.
My life has been worth it.
Although you've always borne a bad name,
this infamy
made the Grand Princess lower her guard against you.
For over ten years,
it kept you and Ayan
living safely in the palace.
That's enough.
But... but I'm afraid they'll say
that killing is addictive.
When I killed him,
it felt very strange.
Very strange.
It's not your fault.
Zhou Hong deserved to die.
My life has been absurd.
Wealth and glory
have long made me a caged bird.
Those sleepless days and nights,
looking at the starry sky,
hoping a star would fall on me.
Did that star fall?
Ever since Ayue came,
I haven't been afraid anymore.
Player's game progress: 70%.
Thanks to His Majesty,
he helped us drive away the drought.
Exactly.
Our emperor,
I don't know when he changed his temper.
He used to collect a fifty percent tax,
now he only collects thirty percent.
The tyrant used to
do nothing good.
We commoners suffered the most.
Things are better now.
Some immortal from out of nowhere
must have cast a spell,
and made our emperor
act like a decent human again.
Exactly.
Look how good our lives are now.
Yuanyuan.
Are they talking about my royal brother?
Yes, they are all praising His Majesty.
My royal brother is amazing.
So many people like him.
When our A'yan grows up,
you should also become someone like His Majesty.
Okay?
Okay.
Have some water.
Yuanyuan, eat.
Fortunately, Your Majesty sent someone to save me.
So the disaster relief went smoothly without any real danger.
You've worked hard, Teacher.
It is my duty.
This way,
Your Majesty's prestige among the people has been largely restored.
The things you taught me when I was young,
I haven't forgotten any of them.
Oh, right.
A'yan has been fussing lately,
wanting to spend the Spring Festival with you.
Would you be willing to come, Teacher?
Is there no palace banquet this year?
With natural disasters occurring year after year,
the people are struggling.
The palace should be frugal.
We'll just gather together this year.
Just having a New Year's atmosphere is good enough.
Then I shall thank Your Majesty first.
Just now at the door,
I ran into the little prince.
He was pulling Eunuch Jingyuan,
insisting on going to the folk market to buy New Year goods.
He said he would give us some
small folk gifts for the New Year.
Gifts?
What is he going to give?
I am really not sure about that.
Does Your Majesty also want to go to the folk market
to pick out some gifts for Lady Cangyue
that are not available in the palace?
Palace rewards and folk trinkets
are too cliché.
If I am going to give a gift,
I will give a unique one.
Thank you, brother.
I love it so much.
This is a gift
for Miss Cangyue.
By the way, Yuanyuan,
didn't you say you'd give me a little airplane?
Where is it?
Airplane?
What is an airplane?
I have never heard of it.
I heard it's something that can fly.
I haven't seen it either.
I've been waiting for a month.
Yuanyuan, you went back on your word.
Rubik's cube, hot pot, airplane.